🎵
Good morning!
Oh, I'm so happy this morning because I woke up with the sun beaming into
my eyes.
This is our bedroom, and you can see that there's so much sun.
Here it's a little bit more blue because we're not facing the sun here, but
it just really makes my day when the sun is shining, And it doesn't happen
so often during the winter time here in Copenhagen.
So you have to really enjoy the days when the sun is shining.
So today we are going for a walk with a dog that we have dog-sitted
once before.
Her name is Sally.
She is a seven months old Bernese Mountain Dog.
When we met her for the first time, I somehow thought that she was going
to be like a small toddler.
or something but no no no she's like a full grown dog she gains i
think one kilo per week and i think she's gonna be like 40 kilos in
total so she's like almost fully grown yeah i'm excited to go and meet her
for the second time i'm just having my little breakfast i'm having some bone broth
this honestly is the best thing ever i drink this every morning i didn't really
know what to expect when i saw people drinking bone broth in the mornings i
was like but it's just it's so soothing and comforting it's honestly not like disgusting
or anything so yeah and i'm having my eggs
HÅ!
She is so strong!
Look at this!
We're trying to teach her to stay next to us.
So we say plets.
But she is just, you know, a baby.
So she wants to play and run around.
Vi
droppte Sally ut, og denne kvelden gjorde mitt dag.
Både å gå med denne kvelden.
Åh, hun er så kjøt!
Og også å møte de hårsene i dag.
Det var to donkere der også.
Og en av horsene kom opp til meg.
Jeg føler at jeg er en horsvisper eller noe.
Jeg er som en horsgurle.
Jeg vokste opp med horser, om du ikke vet det allerede.
Det er så fint å møte denne horsen.
Jeg har ikke sett horser i lang tid.
Men vi går til en bakeri som har den beste fastelandspåler her i Copenhagen.
For i dag er det den store dagen.
Det heter fasteland...
Dagen.
Ja, de har satt på å sælge disse pastere i nye veier, men i dag
er det den siste dagen, hvor det er denne tradisjonen, og det er i stedet
en dansk paste, jeg vet ikke, en bun med en cremig fylling, og det er
så god.
Guys, it is
freezing cold.
There were no spots inside the bakery, because there were so many people.
So we're just sitting here at Islandsbrygge.
So cozy here.
And it's very cute, because there are so many streets that have Icelandic names.
I mean, obviously it's Islandsbrygge.
So it's like the Icelandic area.
Det er mange strider som vi kjenner navnet av, så det er veldig kult.
Vi har den kjære fastelansboller.
Denne er saltet karamell, og denne er pistasjo og raspberry.
Vi har også koffeier som vi må drikke veldig snabbt, for annars blir det koldt.
Åh, herregud, se på dette!
Åh, åh.
Mmh.
Åh, åh, åh.
Det er proper pistasjo.
Wow, proper pistachio.
Ja, you have a lot of green.
This is Grinch.
Damn, han gav oss smaka.
This is high quality stuff.
Worth every penny.
Wow.
Well, I think it's about time that i give you guys a little apartment update
you can see over here this empty room i need to show you because we
just got the floors sanded and you can see the difference this is the before
and this is the after look how gorgeous it looks and also the walls are
freshly painted.
So pretty.
So we've been waiting for a couple of days for this to dry.
So we've been living in our other room with all of our furniture so chaotic.
I'm going to show you.
This is what it looks like.
So this is a closet that was in the other room.
We had to disassemble it to put it in here.
And yeah, just a lot of clothes everywhere and this is even worse.
You should not look at this But yeah, now we're gonna put the closet back
in the other room So we basically have to move everything into this room since
this one is ready so the guys can do the rest of the apartment
So we need to fit everything in here.
So we're gonna start with the closet
so
We
finally finished assembling the closet.
It took a while to get the glass doors on the closet.
They were just so heavy and we had no idea what we were doing but
we managed and I'm so glad because now we can start organizing our clothes because
they have just been laying around everywhere.
But now I'm starving and I'm gonna make dinner and today's video is in collaboration
with HelloFresh.
Tonight we are making Hungarian chicken paprikash.
I am so excited to try this because I've never made it at home but
I tried it once in Budapest and it was absolutely divine.
so I'm excited to make it at home.
It's honestly just so nice not having to think about what to cook for dinner.
I just have this bag ready in my fridge and all of it is pre-portioned
and it's so easy to follow the recipe card.
So let's get into it.
With HelloFresh you simply go on their website, browse through the menu and choose the
recipes you want to cook.
There's always a lot of variety and lately they've added even more healthy recipes to
the menu, so it's easy to choose meals that feel balanced but are still really
comforting.
And most of the dishes we've chosen usually take around 20 to 30 minutes to
make, which honestly makes such a difference after a busy day.
Right now you can save up to 959 kroners on your first five boxes using
my code BIRTA2026.
Just check the link in the description box or scan the QR code on the
screen.
It's Helge's first time trying chicken paprikash.
Very exciting.
It was super simple to make and it looks very yummy.
The paprika flavor is like the smoked paprika is very good.
And then you have a little fresh salad on the side.
Yummy!
this is our new bedroom so exciting funny because we were actually gonna have this
as our living room we were planning on tearing down this wall because the kitchen
is right next door we're gonna have like an open space but we changed our
minds and we're not gonna do it for now at least and it just makes
more sense to have this as the bedroom.
It's also a little bit smaller than the other room and I feel like it
just looks really nice.
It's a little bit similar to our previous apartment, kind of funny.
And also you guys saw in the moving vlog that this closet was left here
when we got the apartment and we were a little bit frustrated but it's actually
been a bit nice because we didn't have anything else in the meantime and closets
can be quite expensive so we're just gonna have it for now.
I think it's it's like decent so we're gonna use it while we figure out
something else.
So yeah it's slowly coming together but the apartment is not fully ready because they
need to sand the floors and paint everything in the rest of the apartment.
They're actually coming in a few hours.
So we're just throwing everything into this room and then we're actually going to go
and stay at a hotel because we won't be able to walk around in this
apartment.
It has to dry for a day or something.
So it's also going to be pretty nice, a little getaway but before I get
ready and pack my bags I'm going to make my new obsession which is this
coconut cloud iced matcha.
I tried it at this pop-up matcha place and I fell in love and I
tried to recreate it a couple of times and I always failed because I didn't
know like what to use.
I tried using coconut milk, but you need to use coconut water and coconut cream.
It's just so refreshing.
It's probably the perfect summer drink.
I'm excited to drink it when the weather is a bit nicer, but I've been
enjoying it nonetheless in the cold winter days.
But I'm going to go and show you how to make it
this is what it looks like when you mix it I don't know if you
can see it is just so creamy
I found the combination so weird when I hadn't tried it.
I was certain that I wouldn't like coconut matcha, but when I tried it, it's
actually really good.
I think this is my new favorite way to drink matcha.
It's probably a bit easier if you own the small whisk, you know, that's just
like a little pen.
That would be probably a lot more convenient than my hand mixer but it does
the job.
We dropped our bags at the hotel and now we're on a hunt for a
lunch spot but we don't really know where to go.
I feel like all of the good spots in Copenhagen are in other neighborhoods and
not like in the city center so we're trying to find something.
Maybe this one.
we
just walked past a really cute store
that sells like accessories jewelry and stuff like that and they sell headbands you know
the plastic headbands where you can kind of push your hair back.
I bought one a few years ago but it recently broke and I just think
it's such a cute accessory so I think we need to go and have a
look.
Look at that!
They're waiting for me.
We're
having some afternoon cookies at the hotel and this hotel room is insane.
I think this might be the most beautiful hotel room I've ever stayed at.
Yeah, the design and...
It's just so cozy but still so chic.
Guys, look what I brought home with me.
So I ended up buying a headband from the store that we walked past.
And there were so many people inside the store, but I've never been there before.
But they have so many cute things, you know, claw clips, hairpins, everything
for like accessories.
Isn't it gorgeous?
I love it.
I love the kind of burgundy color.
I need to show you guys how it looks on my hair.
But it's a little bit dirty.
So I'm sorry about that.
How do you like it?
I think it's so cute.
And I just love being able to put my hair back or like so it's
not in my face.
And it also reminds me of when I was younger because I used to wear
these types of headbands all the time.
Cute!
This was so relaxing.
It's exactly what I needed.
I was only missing my book.
It would have been so cozy to read a book while sitting in the bathtub,
but yeah, I really needed to relax a little bit.
It's been quite stressful the last couple of weeks with the renovations at home.
I mean, it's not big renovations, but yeah, I don't know.
I feel like we've been living out of boxes for a long time.
I mean, we moved in in the beginning of January and it's March now.
It's just because we didn't really know what we wanted to do with the apartment.
We had some like plans or like a vision what we wanted to do.
but it just didn't really make sense and it would have been quite expensive and
we just wanted to start fixing the floors, painting the walls and I think it's
gonna make a really big difference so I'm really excited to show you guys once
we fully settle in and like buy a dining table and chairs and a
sofa.
It's been a very temporary situation for a bit too long so I'm gonna be
so happy when this is over with but we are actually i haven't told you
guys but we are going to cape town in a few days so the plan
was kind of to make the paint and the floors and everything just fully settle
and also because there's a lot of chemical smell in the apartment and i think
it's best to kind of not stay there while everything is drying.
So it was kind of an excuse for us to go somewhere but it's not
only that, we also really really wanted to go somewhere warm and now it's like
the end of summer in South Africa and it's gonna be our first time there
and I am so excited.
I'm I'm obviously gonna be vlogging in Cape Town.
I think I might make two vlogs.
And who knows maybe Helge is also going to be filming something but I don't
know it's been a difficult last few months and I don't know.
I posted a video like last week and that video was actually from December last
year.
It got kind of delayed.
I don't want to get into it but I don't know.
I got a lot of comment that people felt that I was a bit different.
Some people thought that I looked sad and I don't know, it's crazy that you
guys spot these things and I guess that you all just know me so well,
which is just crazy, but it honestly kind of also warms my heart knowing that
you guys like care for me and I don't know.
YouTube is like my safe space and it is truly my favorite platform to share
content on.
But when I haven't been feeling my best, it is sometimes difficult to be sharing
so much of your life and try to show up like super positive and happy
and stuff like that.
When behind the scenes you are maybe struggling.
But yeah, I want to continue posting regularly here on YouTube.
I'm just slowly getting back into the rhythm, but I'm really really excited to go
to Cape Town and film videos for you guys.
I think it's gonna be so amazing.
Okay, anyways, we are gonna go have dinner and there is a Chinese hot spot,
hot pot place literally next to our hotel and people were like sitting down it's
kind of like in the basement and I could see in their bowls some yummy
delicious hot pots with noodles and beef and I was like I'm craving this for
dinner.
So I'm quickly gonna blow dry my hair and get dressed and then we're off
to dinner.
i
had
to go and buy some gum because my mouth was literally burning after this dinner
but i have to say it was absolutely amazing this dinner and this place.
I'm so happy that we walked past it.
It's you know literally next to the hotel but I didn't know that it's basically
where you make your own hot pot so I was a little bit stressed out
when we arrived because I had no idea what to pick or like what would
go well together because you also had to pick out your broth and there were
just so many ingredients but I actually ended up picking a pretty good bowl but
I picked the classic broth she told me that it was going to be spicy
and I asked her if you know she could make it less spicy and she
said like yeah medium I thought that was going to be okay and you can
probably tell from the clip when I took like when I took the first bite
it like right away just kind of burnt my mouth but honestly it was so
good i think i would have enjoyed it a little bit more if it was
just a tiny bit less spicy i was kind of dying the taste was just
so so good and i love the noodles that i picked i don't know if
it's like udon noodles they're a little bit thick and then i tried taboki i
don't know what it's called i have to google i've seen it around it's like
rice cakes that is like shaped i don't know it was just very chewy and
lovely ah so yeah it was honestly a really cool experience i will definitely want
to go there again but yeah we are about to have a cozy night we're
gonna watch the final episode of yellowstone we are on the last episode of season
five which is the last season i'm probably gonna cry but honestly like this has
to be probably my top five favorite tv shows it is so amazing if you
like succession it is like a little bit of a similar vibe it's like a
family and business and cowboys and rivalry between
like people i don't it's so good and also the scenery is just so stunning
this show has kind of given me my spark back for horses i know it
sounds weird but now i'm truly like wow i would love to own horses and
be able to live that lifestyle it's a lot to commit to and it's very
expensive but oh my god that would be an absolute dream of mine.
But yeah, I just wanted to recommend it to you guys because I love it.
It's funny because I would make a heart like this, but I know that a
lot of people would do it like this.
I feel like this is like the new generation.
And then, I don't know about this, this is my generation, I think.
Thank you.